http://www.royalarmouries.org/about-us/governance/policies/cookies/

Skip to main content
Privacy and Cookies Privacy
All of our privacy statements are available to download from our policies page.
Cookies
Our website (royalarmouries.org) places small files (‘cookies’) onto your computer to collect information about how you browse the site.
We use cookies to:
measure how you use the website so it can be updated and improved based on your needs
remember the notifications you’ve seen so that we don’t show them to you again
Essential cookies
These cookies allow the site to function properly. They can be blocked using our cookie control tool but this may cause some parts of the site not to function correctly.
Cookie name
Purpose
Expires
PHPSESSID
Cookie generated by applications based on the PHP language.
End of session
Cookies to measure website usage
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics software (Universal Analytics) to collect information about how you use royalarmouries.org. This information helps us make improvements and meet the needs of its users.
Google Analytics stores information about:
the pages you visit on royalarmouries.org
how long you spend on each royalarmouries.org page
how you got to the site
what you click on while you’re visiting the site
We do not collect or store any personal information that can be used to identify who you are.
We do not allow Google to use or share our analytics. For details, read the
Google Analytics privacy document.
Google Analytics sets the following cookies:
Cookie name
Purpose
Expires
_ga
This helps us count how many people visit by tracking if you’ve visited before
2 years
_gid
This helps us count how many people visit by tracking if you’ve visited before
24 hours
_gat_gtag_UA_114032301_1
Used by Google Analytics to regulate how often analytical data is sent to Google.
1 minute
_gali
Used by Google Analytics to determine which links on a page that are being clicked
1 minute
Opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites.
Newsletter pop-ups
Occassionally we use pop-ups to generate new subscribers to our newsletter. A cookie may be placed to track how many times the pop-up has been seen and how many conversions.
Cookie name
Purpose
Expires
hustle_module_show_count-popup-1
Tracks how many visitors have seen the pop-up and the number of conversions
End of session
Cookies remembering your choices
These cookies remember the choices you made on our website and prevent you from being prompted repeatedly.
Cookie name
Purpose
Expires
ct-ultimate-gdpr-cookie
Records your choice to dismiss/accept the default cookie settings
1 year
inc_optin_popup_long_hidden-1
Records your choice to dismiss the newletter subscription pop-up
1 month
How do I change my cookie settings?
Users can easily control which cookies are placed on their computers using our
cookie tool.
Privacy settings
Use the slider to enable or disable types of cookies want to allow.
You can change these settings at any time. However, this can result in some functions no longer being available. For information on deleting the cookies, please consult your browser’s help function.
Block all
Essentials
Functionality
Analytics
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact form, newsletter and other forms across all pages
This website won't:
Functionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies.Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cart
This website won't:
Analytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies.Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAnalytics: Collect anonymous data about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Collect anonymous data about the device you are using
This website won't:
Advertising: Use information for tailored advertising with third partiesAdvertising: Identify device you are personally usingAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsl Functionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Use information for tailored advertising with third partiesAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesl Advertising: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website won't:
Remember your login details
Save & Close
Preferences can be set when the pop-up first appears by selecting “change privacy settings”, or if you change your mind you can open the cookie control panel by selecting the blue button with the “gear” icon at the bottom right of the screen.
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set, visit aboutcookies or allaboutcookies.
Find out how to manage cookies on popular browsers:
To find information relating to other browsers, visit the browser developer’s website.
TweetShareReddit
Share:
TweetShareReddit
Close this module
Coronavirus (Covid-19) Fort Nelson is open.The White Tower is open.The Royal Armouries Museum in Leeds remains closed.More information
